And with that, we have our completed awards show menu, and just in time, because it looks like the pre-show is just ending.
So, let's go over what we've got here.
We started with our phyllo tartlets with the ricotta, and sundried tomato, and feta, and goat cheese inside--really, really delicious.
Then, we did our puff pastry cheese straws, which you see how it sort of draws your eye up.
You've got very short, small bites of the little smoked salmon canapes, which is a nice contrast in height to the puff pastry cheese straws arranged in this vase, just with some decorative rocks in the bottom.
And then of course we go to the smoked salmon canape, with some creme fraiche which is very creamy, and then the saltiness of the fish, and the nice nutty flavor and texture of the--this so-called "European bread"--which you can then take a little lemon juice to.
And then we finish with our fricos, our parmesan crackers with mache, that baby lettuce, and served in an alternate way in the martini glass with just the same parmesan crisp, but not in the arced format.
So just another guideline to keep in mind: how do you know how many appetizers to make for your party?
If it's not during a mealtime, you want to have at least two to three kinds of appetizers, so in this case, we've got the four.
But at least two to three kinds, and bank on two minimum per person for your party.
If it is in place of a meal, however, you want to have--bank on five to seven different appetizers, and again, two to three per person.